#### Contact

tevansr15@outlook.com

www.linkedin.com/in/tiniecia-goldsmith-b5a2b414 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Communication Verbal

Retail Management

### Languages

English (Professional Working)

# Tiniecia goldsmith

Registered Nurse at Coast Medical Service

North Hollywood, California

## Summary

I am enthusiastic nurse with the skills and abilities necessary to contribute positively to patient care. I possess effective interpersonal skills, oral, and written communication skills as well. I'm a team worker and take pride in my adaptability. As a nurse one take pride in providing the best and safest care to my patients. My goal is to become a CEN and expert that others can rely on with the care one needs.

## Experience

Coast Medical Service Registered Nurse May 2019 - Present (1 year 3 months) Los Angeles, California

Kaiser Permanente Registered Nurse July 2019 - March 2020 (9 months) Los Angeles, California

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
Registered Nurse
December 2016 - February 2020 (3 years 3 months)
Houston, Texas

Memorial Hermann Memorial City RN April 2018 - April 2019 (1 year 1 month) Houston, Texas Area

Tomball Regional Medical Ctr Registered Nurse IMCU November 2015 - June 2017 (1 year 8 months) Houston, Texas Continental Airlines
Flight Attendant
August 2004 - April 2006 (1 year 9 months)
houston,tx

- -Announce and demonstrate safety and emergency procedures such as the use of oxygen masks, seat belts, and life jackets.
- -Answer passengers' questions about flights, aircraft, weather, travel routes and services, arrival times, and/or schedules.
- -Assist passengers in placing carry-on luggage in overhead, garment, or under-seat storage.
- Assist passengers while entering or disembarking the aircraft.
- -Attend preflight briefings concerning weather, altitudes, routes, emergency procedures, crew coordination, lengths of flights, food and beverage services offered, and numbers of passengers.
- -Check to ensure that food, beverages, blankets, reading material, emergency equipment, and other supplies are aboard and are in adequate supply.

### Education

Grambling State University

B.S. Nursing, Nursing (2011 - 2014)

Grambling State University

Marketing, Management · (2002 - 2008)

Tamp Fashion Design School (2003 - 2004)